Alan W. Steelman papers, Inclusive: 1960-2003, Bulk: 1973-1976
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Legislative, 1965-1976, undated; 8
  - 94th Congress, 1975-1976; 2
    - Pending Cases, 1975 (Box 147, Folder 16)
    - Polygraph Tests (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 147, Folder 17)
    - Polygraph Tests (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Postal Reorganization Bill, H.R. 8603, 1976 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Postal Service Subsidy Bill, S. 2844, 1976 (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Prevention of Crimes Against the Elderly, 1976 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Privacy, 1975 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Privacy, 1976 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Privacy Rights and Financial Institutions, 1975 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Private Individual Postage Rate Relief Act, 1975 (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Processed Meat Imports, 1976 (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Prorated Social Security Benefits, 1975 (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - Proxy Voting, 1975 (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - Questionnaires (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 148, Folder 12)
    - Questionnaires (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 148, Folder 13)
    - Questionnaires, 1976 (Box 148, Folder 14)
    - Rape Prevention and Control, 1975 (Box 148, Folder 15)
    - Repeal Health Planning and Resources Act, 1976 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Republican Conference, 1975 (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Rural Post Office Closings, 1976 (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Reform of House Rules, 1974-1976 (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Regulation Reform, 1975 (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Revenue Sharing, 1975-1976 (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - “Save Outdoor America”, 1975 (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - Second Session, 1976 (Box 149, Folder 8)
    - Select Committee on Energy, 1975 (Box 149, Folder 9)
    - Senior Intern Program, 1975 (Box 149, Folder 10)
    - Singles Tax Reform, 1975-1976 (Box 149, Folder 11)
    - Social Security Disability, 1975-1976 (Box 149, Folder 12)
    - Social Security Reform, 1975 (Box 149, Folder 13)
    - Solid Waste Disposal, 1976 (Box 149, Folder 14)
    - State-Owned Crude Oil, 1975 (Box 149, Folder 15)
    - Steelman Office Intern, 1975 (Box 149, Folder 16)
    - Surface Mining, 1975-1976 (Box 149, Folder 17)
    - Sunset Legislation, 1976 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Surveys/Questionnaires, 1976 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Survivors’ Pension Benefits, 1976 (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Task Force on Economic Reform, 1975 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - Task Force on MIA’s, 1975 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Taxes on Small Business Investment Companies, 1975 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Texas Air Control Board, 1975 (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - Texas Wilderness, 1976 (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - Thank You Notes for Votes Cast, 1976 (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - Transportation (1 of 8), 1975-1976 (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - Transportation (2 of 8), 1975-1976 (Box 150, Folder 11)
    - Transportation (3 of 8), 1975-1976 (Box 150, Folder 12)
    - Transportation (4 of 8), 1975-1976 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Transportation (5 of 8), 1975-1976 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Transportation (6 of 8), 1975-1976 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Transportation (7 of 8), 1975-1976 (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Transportation (8 of 8), 1975-1976 (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Transportation, Airline Regulation, 1975-1976 (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Transportation, Federal Express, 1975-1976 (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Transportation, Motor Carrier Reform, 1976 (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Transportation, Truck Weights, 1975 (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Trinity River, 1975 (Box 151, Folder 10)
    - Trinity River, 1976 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - United Nations and Zionism Resolution, 1975 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Postal Service, H.R. 55 & 56, 1975 (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Postal Service, H.R. 2445, 1975 (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Verbatim Congressional Record, 1975 (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Veterans Case, 1975 (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Veterans Civilian Health and Medical Program of the Uniformed Services Benefits, 1976 (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - Veterans Disability Bill (2 bills), 1976 (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - Veterans Education Legislation, 1976 (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - Veterans Home Loan (Case Loan), 1975-1976 (Box 152, Folder 10)
    - Veterans Legislation, 1975-1976 (Box 152, Folder 11)
    - Veterans Mortgage Life Insurance, 1975 (Box 152, Folder 12)
    - Veterans Pensions, 1975-1976 (Box 152, Folder 13)
    - Vietnam Refugee Crisis, 1975 (Box 152, Folder 14)
    - Virgin Islands Constitution, 1975 (Box 152, Folder 15)
    - Vocational Education, 1975 (Box 152, Folder 16)
    - Vote on Changes in House Allowances, 1976 (Box 152, Folder 17)
    - Women in Coast Guard Academy, 1975-1976 (Box 152, Folder 18)
    - Women in Service Academies, 1974-1975 (Box 152, Folder 19)
    - Wild and Scenic Rivers Act, 1976 (Box 152, Folder 20)
  - Topical, 1965-1976; 3
    - General, 1965-1976, undated; 1
      - AEI, Legislative Analysis (1 of 2), 1965-1967 (Box 152, Folder 21)
      - AEI, Legislative Analysis (2 of 2), 1965-1967 (Box 152, Folder 22)
      - Bess (Creative Learning), 1972-1976 (Box 153, Folder 1)
      - Commerce, No Fault (1 of 2), 1974-1976 (Box 153, Folder 2)
      - Commerce, No Fault (2 of 2), 1974-1976 (Box 153, Folder 3)
      - Commerce, No Fault, No. 5313, 1974-1976 (Box 153, Folder 4)
      - Felice, Louis F., 1967-1976 (Box 153, Folder 5)
      - Institute of Politics, 1969-1972 (Box 153, Folder 6)
      - League of United Latin American Citizens, Undated (Box 153, Folder 7)
      - Newspaper Clippings Note, Undated (Box 153, Folder 8)
    - Amtrak, 1972-1976; 2
      - Amtrak vs. Bus Transportation, 1972 (Box 154, Folder 1)
      - Articles, Clippings, Releases, 1973 (Box 154, Folder 2)
      - Articles on Amtrak, 1975 (Box 154, Folder 3)
      - Board of Directors, 1973 (Box 154, Folder 4)
      - Congressional Hearings (1 of 2), 1972 (Box 154, Folder 5)
      - Congressional Hearings (2 of 2), 1972 (Box 154, Folder 6)
      - Congressional Record Remarks, 1973 (Box 154, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, Monaghan, 1972-1973 (Box 154, Folder 8)
      - Dallas-Houston, 1973 (Box 154, Folder 9)
      - General (1 of 3), 1974 (Box 154, Folder 10)
      - General (2 of 3), 1974 (Box 154, Folder 11)
      - General (3 of 3), 1974 (Box 154, Folder 12)
      - General, 1976 (Box 155, Folder 1)
      - General (1 of 3), 1973 (Box 155, Folder 2)
      - General (2 of 3), 1973 (Box 155, Folder 3)
      - General (3 of 3), 1973 (Box 155, Folder 4)
      - General, 1970-1974 (Box 155, Folder 5)
      - Inter-American Subcommittee Report, 1975 (Box 155, Folder 6)
      - Legislative History, 1973 (Box 155, Folder 7)
      - Meeting (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 156, Folder 1)
      - Meeting (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 156, Folder 2)
      - Monaghan Strategy, 1973 (Box 156, Folder 3)
      - National Association of Rail Road Passengers, 1971 (Box 156, Folder 4)
      - National Association of Rail Road Passengers, 1972 (Box 156, Folder 5)
      - Population Comparisons, 1973 (Box 156, Folder 6)
      - Presentation of 2/21/73, 1973 (Box 156, Folder 7)
      - Presentation of 2/22/73, 1973 (Box 156, Folder 8)
      - Schedules, 1973 (Box 156, Folder 9)
      - Texas Rail Road Routes, 1970s (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - Big Thicket, 1973-1976; 3
      - “Amendments Proposed”, 1973 (Box 156, Folder 11)
      - Bill, 1973 (Box 156, Folder 12)
      - Committee Materials, 1973 (Box 156, Folder 13)
      - Environmental Impact Statement, 1973 (Box 156, Folder 14)
      - Environmentalist Package, 1973 (Box 156, Folder 15)
      - Final Bill, 1973 (Box 157, Folder 1)
      - General (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 157, Folder 2)
      - General (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 157, Folder 3)
      - General (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 157, Folder 4)
      - General (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 157, Folder 5)
      - General (1 of 3), 1976 (Box 157, Folder 6)
      - General (2 of 3), 1976 (Box 157, Folder 7)
      - General (3 of 3), 1976 (Box 157, Folder 8)
      - General (1 of 7), 1973 (Box 158, Folder 1)
      - General (2 of 7), 1973 (Box 158, Folder 2)
      - General (3 of 7), 1973 (Box 158, Folder 3)
      - General (4 of 7), 1973 (Box 158, Folder 4)
      - General (5 of 7), 1973 (Box 158, Folder 5)
      - General (6 of 7), 1973 (Box 158, Folder 6)
      - General (7 of 7), 1973 (Box 159, Folder 1)
      - General Information (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 159, Folder 2)
      - General Information (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 159, Folder 3)
      - Interior Department Responses, 1973 (Box 159, Folder 4)
      - Land Costs, 1973 (Box 159, Folder 5)
      - Legislative Counsel, 1973 (Box 159, Folder 6)
      - Redwood Provision Background, 1973 (Box 159, Folder 7)
      - Remarks, 1973 (Box 159, Folder 8)
      - Subcommittee (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 159, Folder 9)
      - Subcommittee (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 159, Folder 10)
      - Subcommittee Testimony (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 160, Folder 1)
      - Subcommittee Testimony (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 160, Folder 2)
      - Testimony, 1973 (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Energy, 1965-1976; 4
      - Alternative Energy Sources (1 of 2), circa 1965-1974 (Box 160, Folder 4)
      - Alternative Energy Sources (2 of 2), circa 1965-1974 (Box 160, Folder 5)
      - General (1 of 3), 1975 April-June (Box 160, Folder 6)
      - General (2 of 3), 1975 April-June (Box 160, Folder 7)
      - General (3 of 3), 1975 April-June (Box 161, Folder 1)
      - Arab Oil Embargo, 1973 (Box 161, Folder 2)
      - Conservation and Development, 1975 (Box 161, Folder 3)
      - Daylight Savings Time, 1974 (Box 161, Folder 4)
      - Energy Divestiture (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 161, Folder 5)
      - Energy Divestiture (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 161, Folder 6)
      - Energy Task Force, 1973 (Box 161, Folder 7)
      - Energy and Impeachment, 1974 (Box 161, Folder 8)
      - Energy No. 121, 1974 (Box 161, Folder 9)
      - Energy No. 116, 1974 (Box 162, Folder 1)
      - Energy No. 114, 1974 (Box 162, Folder 2)
      - Energy No. 112, 1974 (Box 162, Folder 3)
      - Energy No. 107, 1973 (Box 162, Folder 4)
      - Energy No. 102, 1973 (Box 162, Folder 5)
      - Energy No. 101, 1973 (Box 162, Folder 6)
      - Energy No. 98, 1973 (Box 162, Folder 7)
      - Energy No. 97, 1973 (Box 162, Folder 8)
      - Energy No. 96, 1973 (Box 162, Folder 9)
      - Energy No. 95, 1973 (Box 162, Folder 10)
      - General (1 of 12), 1973 (Box 162, Folder 11)
      - General (2 of 12), 1973 (Box 162, Folder 12)
      - General (3 of 12), 1973 (Box 162, Folder 13)
      - General (4 of 12), 1973 (Box 162, Folder 14)
      - General (5 of 12), 1973 (Box 162, Folder 15)
      - General (6 of 12), 1973 (Box 163, Folder 1)
      - General (7 of 12), 1973 (Box 163, Folder 2)
      - General (8 of 12), 1973 (Box 163, Folder 3)
      - General (9 of 12), 1973 (Box 163, Folder 4)
      - General (10 of 12), 1973 (Box 163, Folder 5)
      - General (11 of 12), 1973 (Box 163, Folder 6)
      - General (12 of 12), 1973 (Box 163, Folder 7)
      - General (1 of 10), 1974 (Box 163, Folder 8)
      - General (2 of 10), 1974 (Box 164, Folder 1)
      - General (3 of 10), 1974 (Box 164, Folder 2)
      - General (4 of 10), 1974 (Box 164, Folder 3)
      - General (5 of 10), 1974 (Box 164, Folder 4)
      - General (6 of 10), 1974 (Box 164, Folder 5)
      - General (7 of 10), 1974 (Box 164, Folder 6)
      - General (8 of 10), 1974 (Box 164, Folder 7)
      - General (9 of 10), 1974 (Box 164, Folder 8)
      - General (10 of 10), 1974 (Box 164, Folder 9)
      - General, 1974-1975 (Box 164, Folder 10)
      - General, 1975 (Box 165, Folder 1)
      - General (1 of 6), 1976 (Box 165, Folder 2)
      - General (2 of 6), 1976 (Box 165, Folder 3)
      - General (3 of 6), 1976 (Box 165, Folder 4)
      - General (4 of 6), 1976 (Box 165, Folder 5)
      - General (5 of 6), 1976 (Box 165, Folder 6)
      - General (6 of 6), 1976 (Box 165, Folder 7)
      - General (1 of 4), 1975 January-March (Box 166, Folder 1)
      - General (2 of 4), 1975 January-March (Box 166, Folder 2)
      - General (3 of 4), 1975 January-March (Box 166, Folder 3)
      - General (4 of 4), 1975 January-March (Box 166, Folder 4)
      - General (1 of 4), 1975 July-September (Box 166, Folder 5)
      - General (2 of 4), 1975 July-September (Box 166, Folder 6)
      - General (3 of 4), 1975 July-September (Box 167, Folder 1)
      - General (4 of 4), 1975 July-September (Box 167, Folder 2)
      - Natural Gas, 1976 (Box 167, Folder 3)
      - Nuclear, 1976 (Box 167, Folder 4)
      - General (1 of 2), 1975 October-December (Box 167, Folder 5)
      - General (2 of 2), 1975 October-December (Box 167, Folder 6)
      - Oil and Gas Decontrol & Energy Conference (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 167, Folder 7)
      - Oil and Gas Decontrol & Energy Conference (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 168, Folder 1)
      - Oil Decontrol, 1975 (Box 168, Folder 2)
      - Outer Continental Shelf, 1976 (Box 168, Folder 3)
      - Price Controls, 1974 (Box 168, Folder 4)
      - Propane, 1974 (Box 168, Folder 5)
      - Publications, 1974 (Box 168, Folder 6)
      - Rationing (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 168, Folder 7)
      - Rationing (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 169, Folder 1)
      - Rollbacks Emergency Act, 1974 (Box 169, Folder 2)
      - Vote on Deregulation of Natural Gas, 1976 (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - Trinity River, 1965-1976; 5
      - Anti, 1973 (Box 169, Folder 4)
      - Aubrey & Lakeview Testimony, 1974 (Box 169, Folder 5)
      - Bridges, 1973 (Box 169, Folder 6)
      - Corps of Engineers, 1973-1975 (Box 169, Folder 7)
      - De-authorization, 1974 (Box 169, Folder 8)
      - Elm Fork State Park, 1972-1975 (Box 169, Folder 9)
      - Government Accounting Office, 1972-1973 (Box 169, Folder 10)
      - General, 1972-1973 (Box 169, Folder 11)
      - General (1 of 6), 1973 (Box 170, Folder 1)
      - General (2 of 6), 1973 (Box 170, Folder 2)
      - General (3 of 6), 1973 (Box 170, Folder 3)
      - General (4 of 6), 1973 (Box 170, Folder 4)
      - General (5 of 6), 1973 (Box 170, Folder 5)
      - General (6 of 6), 1973 (Box 170, Folder 6)
      - General (1 of 3), 1971-1974 (Box 171, Folder 1)
      - General (2 of 3), 1971-1974 (Box 171, Folder 2)
      - General (3 of 3), 1971-1974 (Box 171, Folder 3)
      - General (1 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 171, Folder 4)
      - General (2 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 171, Folder 5)
      - General (3 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 171, Folder 6)
      - General Information (1 of 3), circa 1965-1975 (Box 171, Folder 7)
      - General Information (2 of 3), circa 1965-1975 (Box 172, Folder 1)
      - General Information (3 of 3), circa 1965-1975 (Box 172, Folder 2)
      - Information, 1973-1974 (Box 172, Folder 3)
      - Lakeview, 1975 (Box 172, Folder 4)
      - Legislation (1 of 2), 1972-1974 (Box 172, Folder 5)
      - Legislation (2 of 2), 1972-1974 (Box 172, Folder 6)
      - Legislation, 1973-1976 (Box 172, Folder 7)
      - River Brief, 1972-1973 (Box 172, Folder 8)
      - Steelman Bills, 1973 (Box 172, Folder 9)
      - Townlake Project, 1974 (Box 173, Folder 1)
      - Trinity River Testimony, 1972-1973 (Box 173, Folder 2)
      - Trinity Wild & Scenic Rivers, 1972-1973 (Box 173, Folder 3)
      - Water Resources Approbation, 1973 (Box 173, Folder 4)
- Press, 1973-1976, undated; 9
  Overall, the Press series remains in good condition, though the Columns, Magazines, and Topical subseries are in poor condition compared to the Releases subseries. The Columns subseries contains articles written by and about Steelman. Steelman's achievements are highlighted in the Magazines subseries, which includes pieces on him from outlets such as TIME and the Harvard Political Review. The Releases subseries constitutes the largest part of the series and has alphabetical ordering according to the title of the release. A conglomeration of documents on subjects from Steelman's talking points to a pamphlet introducing Steelman from the first session of the 93rd Congress comprise the Topical subseries.
  - Columns, 1973-1974, 1976; 1
    - Steelman Articles and Editorials, 1973 Winter (Box 173, Folder 5)
    - “Trunkline Material”, 1973 (Box 173, Folder 6)
    - Young Republican, Column, 1974 (Box 173, Folder 7)
  - Magazines, 1973-1974, 1976-1977; 2
    - Harvard Political Review, Winter 1973 (Box 173, Folder 8)
    - PrimeTime, March 1977 (Box 173, Folder 9)
    - Texas Monthly, May 1976 (Box 173, Folder 10)
    - TIME, July 1974 (Box 173, Folder 11)
  - Newsletters, 1973-1976; 3
    - General, 1973 (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - General, 1974 (Box 174, Folder 2)
    - General, 1975 (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - General, 1976 (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - Young Adult Republicans Club of Dallas, 1973 (Box 174, Folder 5)
  - Releases, 1973-1976; 4
    - “ABC’s of Texas”, 1973 (Box 174, Folder 6)
    - ABC Land Use Program, 1975 (Box 174, Folder 7)
    - “ACA Senate Endorsement”, 1976 (Box 174, Folder 8)
    - “ACU Endorsement Release”, 1976 (Box 174, Folder 9)
    - Alan’s CAB Testimony, 1974 (Box 174, Folder 10)
    - Alan’s Senate Announcement Statement, 1976 (Box 174, Folder 11)
    - Alaskan Pipeline Statement, 1973 (Box 174, Folder 12)
    - “Amtrack Extension”, 1974 (Box 174, Folder 13)
    - “Amtrack Letter”, 1973 (Box 174, Folder 14)
    - “Amtrak Letter to Byrd”, 1974 (Box 174, Folder 15)
    - “Amtrack Panel Decision, 1973 (Box 174, Folder 16)
    - “Amtrack Release”, 1973 (Box 174, Folder 17)
    - Amtrack Release, Dallas Press Conference, 1973 (Box 174, Folder 18)
    - “Amtrack Speeches”, 1973 (Box 174, Folder 19)
    - “Alan Steelman Financial Disclosure”, 1975 (Box 174, Folder 20)
    - “Alan Steelman Letter to Ford (Energy)”, 1975 (Box 174, Folder 21)
    - “Alan Steelman Letter to Rhodes”, 1975 (Box 174, Folder 22)
    - “AS Meeting with Welch”, 1974 (Box 174, Folder 23)
    - “Alan Steelman on Older Americans Housing”, 1975 (Box 174, Folder 24)
    - “Alan Steelman on RNC TV Show”, 1975 (Box 174, Folder 25)
    - “Alan Steelman on 1976 Proposed Budget”, 1975 (Box 174, Folder 26)
    - Assistant Floor Leader Statement, 1973 (Box 174, Folder 27)
    - Auto CAPS Letter with Tower, 1974 (Box 174, Folder 28)
    - Average Financial Effect, 1975 (Box 174, Folder 29)
    - “Banik Bill Release”, 1973 (Box 174, Folder 30)
    - Banking and Currency Testimony, 1974 (Box 174, Folder 31)
    - Big Thicket Acquisition, 1975 (Box 174, Folder 32)
    - “Big Thicket Bill Introduction”, 1973 (Box 174, Folder 33)
    - “Big Thicket, Committee Passage”, 1973 (Box 174, Folder 34)
    - Big Thicket/GAO Investigation, 1976 (Box 174, Folder 35)
    - “Big Thicket Legislative Taking”, 1975 (Box 174, Folder 36)
    - Big Thicket Memo, 1976 (Box 174, Folder 37)
    - “Big Thicket Statement”, 1973 (Box 174, Folder 38)
    - “Big Thicket: ‘Suspension’”, 1973 (Box 174, Folder 39)
    - “Box Car Shortage Speech”, 1973 (Box 174, Folder 40)
    - Brucellosis Testimony, 1976 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - “Budget Release”, 1973 (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - “Busing and Letter to Ford”, 1975 (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - “Busing Discharge Petition”, 1973 (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - “Busing and Policy Committee”, 1975 (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - “Busing Cosigners”, 1975 (Box 175, Folder 6)
    - “Busing Cosigners”, 1975 (Box 175, Folder 7)
    - Butz Bread Shortage Letter, 1974 (Box 175, Folder 8)
    - Call Bill, Bill Status, 1974 (Box 175, Folder 9)
    - “Cambodian Cutoff Vote Release”, 1973 (Box 175, Folder 10)
    - “Casey EPA Letter”, 1975 (Box 175, Folder 11)
    - “CHAMPUS Bill Release”, 1975 (Box 175, Folder 12)
    - “CIA Testimony Statement”, 1975 (Box 175, Folder 13)
    - Classification Testimony, 1974 (Box 175, Folder 14)
    - “Cohen Energy”, 1973 (Box 175, Folder 15)
    - “Committee Assignment Release”, 1973 (Box 175, Folder 16)
    - “Committee on Intelligence Oversight”, 1975 (Box 175, Folder 17)
    - “Commission on Regulatory Reform”, 1975 (Box 175, Folder 18)
    - “Committee Reform Resolution”, 1974 (Box 175, Folder 19)
    - Conference Report on Home Health Care, H.R.14214, 1974 (Box 175, Folder 20)
    - “Congressional Pay Raise Discharge Petition”, 1974 (Box 175, Folder 21)
    - “Congressional Wage Increase”, 1973 (Box 175, Folder 22)
    - “Congressman of the Month: May”, 1973 (Box 175, Folder 23)
    - “Connally Release”, 1973 (Box 175, Folder 24)
    - “Connally Statement”, 1973 (Box 175, Folder 25)
    - “Conservation Fund Letter”, 1974 (Box 175, Folder 26)
    - “Controls Defeat in Senate Committee”, 1974 (Box 175, Folder 27)
    - “Countdown on Controls”, 1974 (Box 175, Folder 28)
    - “Cowboy Poem and Colleague”, 1973 (Box 175, Folder 29)
    - “Daily Interamerican Letter”, 1974 (Box 175, Folder 30)
    - “Dallas-Based Press Releases”, 1974 (Box 175, Folder 31)
    - “Dallas SER Contract”, 1974 (Box 175, Folder 32)
    - “Ditchley Foundation London”, 1974 (Box 175, Folder 33)
    - “Duck Creek GAO Report”, 1976 (Box 175, Folder 34)
    - “Duck Creek Investigation”, 1975 (Box 175, Folder 35)
    - “Dunlop Steel Letter”, 1973 (Box 175, Folder 36)
    - “Earle Cabell Committee Passage”, 1973 (Box 175, Folder 37)
    - Earle Cabell Proposal, 1973 (Box 175, Folder 38)
    - “Economic Stabilization Hearings”, 1973 (Box 175, Folder 39)
    - “Economic Stabilization Repeal”, 1973 (Box 175, Folder 40)
    - “Elderly Crime Bill”, 1976 (Box 175, Folder 41)
    - “Elderly Housing Recommendation”, 1974 (Box 175, Folder 42)
    - “Energy Message Release”, 1973 (Box 175, Folder 43)
    - “Environmental Press Conference”, 1975 (Box 175, Folder 44)
    - “ERDA [Energy Research & Development Administration] Cosponsorship”, 1973 (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - “ERDA Co-sponsor Release”, 1974 (Box 176, Folder 2)
    - ESC Vice Chairman Release, 1975 (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - Estate Tax Bill, 1976 (Box 176, Folder 4)
    - Export Import Bank Bill, 1974 (Box 176, Folder 5)
    - “FBI Director Statement”, 1973 (Box 176, Folder 6)
    - “FDA Bill”, 1974 (Box 176, Folder 7)
    - FEC Reorganization Bill, 1976 (Box 176, Folder 8)
    - “Federal Paperwork Relief Act”, 1974 (Box 176, Folder 9)
    - Financial Disclosure Amendments, 1974 (Box 176, Folder 10)
    - “Financial Disclosure Testimony”, 1976 (Box 176, Folder 11)
    - “Findley Bill Release”, 1973 (Box 176, Folder 12)
    - “Ford Candidacy Announcement”, 1975 (Box 176, Folder 13)
    - “Ford Confirmation”, 1973 (Box 176, Folder 14)
    - “Foreign Aid Barter Bill”, 1974 (Box 176, Folder 15)
    - “Freedom from Military Surveillance”, 1974 (Box 176, Folder 16)
    - “Full Financial Disclosure”, 1974 (Box 176, Folder 17)
    - “Full Financial Disclosure”, 1975 (Box 176, Folder 18)
    - “GAO/Ft. Hood Investigation”, 1976 (Box 176, Folder 19)
    - “GAO/Big Thicket Report”, 1976 (Box 176, Folder 20)
    - “GAO Study Release”, 1976 (Box 176, Folder 21)
    - “Garland HUD Selection”, 1974 (Box 176, Folder 22)
    - “Gold Ownership Bill”, 1974 (Box 176, Folder 23)
    - “Government in the Sunshine”, 1975 (Box 176, Folder 24)
    - “Government OPS: Subcommittees”, 1973 (Box 176, Folder 25)
    - Graphics Pending, Undated (Box 176, Folder 26)
    - “Guardian of Small Business”, 1976 (Box 176, Folder 27)
    - “Hatch Act Video Sustained”, 1976 (Box 176, Folder 28)
    - “Home Health Care Bill”, 1974 (Box 176, Folder 29)
    - Highway Trust Fund, 1973 (Box 176, Folder 30)
    - “Hispanic-American Resolution”, 1976 (Box 176, Folder 31)
    - Home Health Care Sponsors, 1974 (Box 176, Folder 32)
    - “Home Health Services Bill”, 1975 (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - Hospital Release, 1973 (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - “House Resolution on Controls”, 1974 (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - INS Regional Office Letter, 1974 (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - “IRS 1040 Forms Error”, 1976 (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - “Johnson Death Release”, 1973 (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - “Johnson Eulogy: Record”, 1973 (Box 177, Folder 7)
    - "Joint Cong. Comm. on Int. Over”, 1974 (Box 177, Folder 8)
    - “Joint Funding Simplification”, 1974 (Box 177, Folder 9)
    - “Krueger Amendments”, 1976 (Box 177, Folder 10)
    - Land Use Planning Act, 1975 (Box 177, Folder 11)
    - Land Use Press, 1975 (Box 177, Folder 12)